http://www.radiusdisplay.com/info/privacy_policy/

my account
my cart (0)
Products
A/V Accessory CoversCatchbox CoversDual Post Stand and Base CoversDual Post Stand Base MatsPole CoversSpeaker CoversSpeaker Stand CoversTruss CoversBackdrop and Siderail DrapesPleated Backdrop DrapesPleated Side Rail DrapesRod Pocket Backdrop DrapesRod Pocket Side Rail DrapesBackdropsRasterPrint Flat Backdrop OverlayRasterPrint MaxiVision BackdropScreen Print MaxiVision BackdropXPressScan MaxiVision BackdropScreen Print MultiVision BackdropBanner StandsBanner Pole SystemBanner Pole System HardwareBanner Pole System KitsBanner Pole System Replacement GraphicsAdjustable Portable Pole SystemAdjustable Portable Pole HardwareAdjustable Portable Pole KitsAdjustable Portable Pole Replacement GraphicsAscend Retractable Graphic SystemAscend™ HardwareAscend™ KitsAscend™ Replacement GraphicsECO Banner StandECO™ HardwareECO™ KitsECO™ Replacement GraphicsEcono-L Banner StandEcono-L™ HardwareEcono-L™ KitsEcono-L™ Replacement GraphicsRasterPrint Portable Banner StandPortable Banner Stand HardwarePortable Banner Stand Replacement GraphicsRoll-Up Banner StandRoll-up Banner Stand HardwareRoll-up Banner Stand KitsRoll-up Banner Stand Replacement GraphicsSlim StandsSlimStand™ KitsSlimStand™ HardwareSlimStand™ Replacement GraphicsSlim Stand MiniSlimStand™ Mini KitsSlimStand™ Mini HardwareSlimStand™ Mini Replacement GraphicsTilt™ Banner StandTilt™ KitsTilt™ HardwareTilt™ Replacement GraphicsX-Stand™X-Stand™ KitsX-Stand™ HardwareX-Stand™ Replacement GraphicsCart and Stand SkirtingCustom Cart SkirtsProjection Stand CoversProjection Stand SkirtsTwill Cart SkirtsCustom Cart CoversClips1/2" Clips3/4" ClipsOmni II© ClipsBackdrop ClipsLifetime© ClipsCountersCase-2-CounterRadius CounterPortable TableDirector ChairsRasterPrint Director ChairScreen Print Director ChairUnprinted Director ChairXPressScan Director ChairDrape KitsProjection Screen Drape KitsTripod Screen Drape KitsTripod Screen SkirtsDrapeScape™DrapeScape™ OriginalDrapeScape Cuts™DrapeScape™ AccessoriesFlagsFeather FlagsFeather Flag HardwareFeather Flag KitsFeather Flag Replacement GraphicsTeardrop FlagsTeardrop Flag HardwareTeardrop Flag KitsTeardrop Flag Replacement GraphicsFolding StackablesFolding Stackables AccessoriesFS Mini DisplayHanging BannersHanging Banner StructuresHanging Structure KitsHanging Structure HardwareHanging Structure Replacement GraphicsHospitality Accessory CoversBeverage Dispenser CoversBus Tub CoversTrash Can CoversTray CoversTray Stand CoversLiterature StandsNapkins,Table & Banquet clothsNapkinsWhite NapkinsQuick Ship Program NapkinsTable & Banquet clothsQuick Ship Program TableclothsWhite TableclothsPipe and Drape 1.01.0 Upright Replacement Parts1.0 Bases1.0 Carry Off Drapes1.0 Crossbar Replacement Parts1.0 Crossbars1.0 Hardware Dollies1.0 Pipe and Drape Packages1.0 UprightsPipe and Drape 2.0®2.0® Accessories2.0® Crossbars2.0® Accessory Kit2.0® Uprights2.0® Bases2.0® Pipe & Drape Packages2.0® Hardware Dollies2.0® Carry Off DrapesRasterprint Fabric SystemRasterprint Fabric System KitsRasterprint Fabric System AccessoriesRasterprint Portable BackwallRasterPrint Portable Backwall HardwareRasterPrint Portable Backwall KitsRasterPrint Portable Backwall Replacement GraphicsRasterprint Portable Graphics System10' RPGS Back Wall10' RPGS Curved Back Wall6' RPGS Table Top8' RPGS Back Wall8' RPGS Curved Back Wall8' RPGS Table Top8' RPGS TowerAccessoriesShipping Cases and BagsCarpetbaggerExpandable Shipping CasesShipping CasesTote BagsWacky Pak CaseSilicone Edge GraphicsLuma™XPress Pop-Up SEGXpress Pop-Up SEG HardwareXPress Pop-Up SEG KitsXPress Pop-Up SEG Replacement GraphicsXPress Modular SEGTraditional SEG LightboxesFabric SystemStage SkirtingAdjustable SkirtingStage and Non-Standard Table SkirtingStretch CoversRasterPrint Stretch CoversScreen Print Stretch CoversUnprinted Stretch CoversHolidayTable RunnersRasterPrint Table RunnerScreen Print Table RunnerXPress Scan Table RunnerTable SkirtingAccent ValancesAustrian StyleVictorian StyleFitted Skirt and Topper SetsLuster SetsCameo SetsSatin SetsTwill SetsMobile Skirt Caddy and Skirt HangersPrinted SkirtingRasterPrint MaxiVision SkirtingScreen Print MaxiVision SkirtingXPress Scan MaxiVIsion SkirtingScreen Print MultiVision SkirtingSkirting (Standard Sizes)Cameo SkirtingLuster SkirtingTwill SkirtingSatin SkirtingSkirting (By The Foot)Cameo Per Foot SkirtingLuster Per Foot SkirtingTwill Per Foot SkirtingSatin Per Foot SkirtingTable ToppersCameo ToppersLuster ToppersTwill ToppersSatin ToppersDURA™ ToppersTwo-Tier SkirtingCameo Skirting SetsLuster Skirting SetsSatin Skirting SetsTwill Skirting SetsTable Top DisplaysMini Table FlagsMini Table Flag HardwareMini Table Flag KitsMini Table Flag Replacement GraphicsMini X-StandMini Slim StandTable HeaderTable Header HardwareTable Header Replacement GraphicsMini Rollup Banner StandsTension GraphicsCurvo™ BackwallCurvo™ Table TopTentsTent HardwareTent KitsTent Replacement GraphicsThrow CoversCrissCross CoverPrinted CrissCross™ CoversUnprinted CrissCross™ CoversDura ThrowPrinted DURA™ Throw CoversUnprinted DURA™ Throw CoversRasterPrint HD Throw CoverFully PrintedFront Only PrintedRound Throw CoversRound Twill Throw CoversRound DURA™ Throw CoversRound Satin Throw CoversRound Luster Throw CoversRound Cameo Throw CoversScreen Print Throw CoversUnprinted Throw CoversUnprinted Twill Throw CoversUnprinted Satin Throw CoversUnprinted Luster Throw CoversUnprinted Cameo Throw CoversUnprinted DURA™ Throw CoversXPress Scan Throw CoverCloseout DealsBanner Stand DealsD4 DealsFlexpo DealsUsed Parts DealsNew Parts DealsFolding Stackables DealsPPE ItemsFace MasksSignageHome Office
Information
Price Guide Branded
Price Guide Unbranded
Imprint Methods
Swatch Cards
Fabrics
Art
Production
Privacy Policy
Radius Display Products has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website http://www.radiusdp.com.
As a convenience to you, and to further enhance your online experience, this site may contain links to other sites. Radius Display Products is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Check any privacy policy on the target site before giving out personal information.
What We Collect and How We Use It
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information, and to help provide you with a relevant online visit to the site. Cookies are used to further enhance the visitors browsing experience.
Our online registration and information request pages ask visitors for contact information (like their name, phone, address, and email address). We use contact data from these forms to send the user information about our company and our products. The visitor's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. This information may be forwarded to one of our resellers or outside sales representatives solely for the purpose of following up on your request for information on our products. We never make this information available to third parties outside our sales network. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise share your information with outside parties beyond our immediate sales network.
If you arrive at this website by clicking on a link in one of our broadcast emails, we may track your entry point in order to provide a more relevant online experience and to measure the effectiveness of our marketing.
Opting Out of Our System
This site gives users the following options for modifying information previously provided, or to opt-out of any or all of our marketing communication channels. When contacting us, please include your contact number (first line on mailing label or last line in broadcast email), or a recent job or invoice number, to aid us in identifying you in our database and verifying your identity. Also tell us if you want us to stop contacting you via mail, fax, e-mail, or all. You may also use the following options to contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or the practices of this site.
Conventional Mail:
Webmaster
Radius Display Products
800 Fabric X-Press Way
Dallas TX 75234
Phone:
972-406-1221
Fax:
972-406-1321
